Finding Aid for University of Michigan News and Information Services Photographs, 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series C 1961-1997, 35mm negatives
  - No. 5431 to No. 5566 June 1978-September 1978 (Box C37)
  - No. 5567 to No. 5725 September 1978-November 1978 (Box C38)
  - No. 5726 to No. 5870 December 1978-March 1979 (Box C39)
  - No. 5871 to No. 5992 March 1979-May 1979 (Box C40)
  - No. 5993 to No. 7015 July 1979-October 1979 (Box C41)
  - No. 7016 to No. 7140 October 1979-January 1980 (Box C42)
  - No. 7141 to No. 7255 January 1980-May 1980 (Box C43)
  - No. 7256 to No. 7390 May 1980-August 1980 (Box C44)
  - No. 7391 to No. 7510 August 1980-October 1980 (Box C45)
  - No. 7511 to No. 7668 October 1980-February 1981 (Box C46)
  - No. 7669 to No. 7815 February 1981-June 1981 (Box C47)
  - No. 7816 to No. 796,1 June 1981-September 1981 (Box C48)
  - No. 7962 to No. 8079 September 1981-December 1981 (Box C49)
  - No. 8080 to No. 8204 December 1981-May 1982 (Box C50)
  - No. 8205 to No. 8322 May 1982-September 1982 (Box C51)
  - No. 8323 to No. 8444 September 1982-January 1983 (Box C52)
  - No. 8445 to No. 8551 January 1983-May 1983 (Box C53)
  - No. 8552 to No. 8672 April 1983-November 1983 (Box C54)
  - No. 8673 to No. 8795 September 1983-January 1984 (Box C55)
  - No. 8796 to No. 8928 January 1984-April 1984 (Box C56)
  - No. 8929 to No. 9031 April 1984-July 1984 (Box C57)
  - No. 9032 to No. 9129 July 1984-October 1984 (Box C58)
  - No. 9130 to No. 9239 October 1984-January 1985 (Box C59)
  - No. 9240 to No. 9376 January 1985-June 1985 (Box C60)
  - No. 9377 to No. 9453 June 1985-October 1985 (Box C61)
  - No. 9454 to No. 9559 October 1985-March 1986 (Box C62)
  - No. 9560 to No. 9667 March 1986-September 1986 (Box C63)
  - No. 9668 to No. 9781 September 1986-February 1987 (Box C64)
  - No. 9782 to No. 9890 February 1987-September 1987 (Box C65)
  - No. 9891 to No. 9973 September 1987-December 1987 (Box C66)
  - No. 9974 to No. 10100 December 1987-May 1988 (Box C67)
  - No. 10101 to No. 10230 May 1988-September 1988 (Box C68)
  - No. 10231 to No. 10339 September 1988-December 1988 (Box C69)
  - No. 10340 to No. 10406 December 1988-June 1989 (Box C70)
  - No. 10407 to No. 10518 June 1989-September 1989 (Box C71)
  - No. 10519 to No. 10622 September 1989-October 1989 (Box C72)
  - No. 10623 to No. 10757 October 1989-March 1990 (Box C73)
  - No. 10758 to No. 10897 March 1990-August 1990 (Box C74)
  - No. 10898 to No. 11012 July 1990-October 1990 (Box C75)
  - No. 11013 to No. 11144 October 1990-January 1991 (Box C76)
  - No. 11145 to No. 11290 January 1991-June 1991 (Box C77)
  - No. 11291 to No. 11409 June 1991-November 1991 (Box C78)
  - No. 11410 to No. 11557 November 1991-April 1992 (Box C79)
  - No. 11558 to No. 11692 April 1992-September 1992 (Box C80)
  - No. 11693 to No. 11818 September 1992-January 1993 (Box C81)
  - No. 11819 to No. 11947 January 1993-May 1993 (Box C82)
  - No. 11948 to No. 12040 May 1993-September 1993 (Box C83)
  - No. 12041 to No. 12144 September 1993-Jan 1994 (Box C84)
  - No. 12145 to No. 12261 January 1994-August 1994 (Box C85)
  - No. 12262 to No. 12364 August 1994-November 1994 (Box C86)
  - No. 12365 to No. 12482 November 1994-March 1995 (Box C87)
  - No. 12483 to No. 12607 March 1995-September 1995 (Box C88)
  - No. 12608 to No. 12720 September 1995-January 1996 (Box C89)
  - No. 12721 to No. 12826 January 1996-April 1996 (Box C90)
  - No. 12827 to No. 12931 April 1996-July 1996 (Box C91)
  - No. 12932 to No. 13026 July 1996-September 1996 (Box C92)
  - No. 13027 to No. 13133 September 1996-December 1996 (Box C93)
  - No. 13134 to No. 13227 December 1996-April 1997 (Box C94)
  - No. 13228 to No. 13324 April 1997-June 1997 (Box C95)
  - No. 13325 to No. 13375 June 1997-July 1997 (Box C96)
- Series D 1946-2006 (Faculty Portraits)
  This series, commonly known as "Series D" is part of the News and Information Services photographs collection, which consists of several other series often based on format such as the size of the negatives (4x5 or 35mm) or content (general campus photography or aerial photographs). Series D consists of black and white 4x5 inch negatives and 1-1/4 x 2-1/4 inch prints and negatives of faculty and staff (and some student) portraits alphabetically arranged.
  A comprehensive index for the entire series was created in 2007. It replaces what had been a partial index covering less than half of the content (two additions were received after the initial index was prepared). Based on information supplied on the original envelopes, the listing includes faculty/staff name, department or unit (when provided) and date(s) of the portrait. Bentley Library negative numbers are included (if applicable). See the separate finding aid for News and Information Services, Series D, faculty and staff portraits
- Series E (Photographic Prints, Slides, Negatives)
  SERIES E (6 linear ft. plus one oversize box; ca. 1950s-1990s) consists of Photographic prints of a variety of campus subjects, (mainly black and white) some of which were received by News and Information Services from non-university photographers. Box 17 contains color slides.
  Images include documentation of a wide range of activities and special events (such as athletics, commencement, demonstrations in the 1960s), views of buildings and facilities, and photographs of people in both formal and informal settings. Also included in the series are color slides of the University Orchestra trip to Russia, football games in 1971, and various campus scenes.
  Photographs with numbers on the back produced before August, 1974 usually have corresponding negatives located in Series B or Series C. An index to Series E is included in the inventory section of this finding aid. Subject headings, for the most part, were maintained as devised by News and Information Services.
  A significant addition to the original Series E consists primarily of negatives taken of the School of Business Administration for Pringle Smith, editor of the Business School's Dividend magazine. These negatives retain their original filing scheme and are organized alphabetically by subject. A date is also included because it appears that while the files were organized alphabetically they were also separated by the years in which they were produced. Included in this series are two linear feet of general negatives. They cover a range of subjects, with large sections pertaining to the construction of the Taubman Medical Center, Law Library and the Law School in the early 1980s. These negatives are organized alphabetically based on their subject heading. There is also a box of slides included in this series. These slides cover a wide range of campus activities, many deal with science and engineering trips or experiments, and a small number document John F. Kennedy's famous Peace Corps speech on the steps of the Union in 1960. There are small sub-series relating to the solar car within the print series and the slide series. The slides are housed in plastic sheets and are organized alphabetically by subject.
  - Print Files circa 1950s-1990s
    - Academic Affairs (Box E1)
    - Aerial Views (Box E1)
    - Affirmative Action (Box E1)
    - Afro-American Studies (Box E1)
    - Alumni Association (Box E1)
    - Ann Arbor, City of (Box E1)
    - Art / Exhibits / Galleries (Box E1)
    - Art Fair (Box E1)
    - Astronomy (Box E1)
    - Athletics
      - Buildings / Facilities (Box E1)
      - Camps (Box E1)
      - Field Hockey (Box E1)
      - Football (Folder 1) (Box E1)
      - Football (Folder 2) (Box E2)
      - Golf (Box E2)
      - Gymnastics (Box E2)
      - Hockey (Box E2)
      - Miscellaneous (Box E2)
      - Rose Bowl 1979 (Box E2)
      - Soccer (Box E2)
      - Swimming (Box E2)
      - Tennis (Box E2)
      - Track and Field (Box E2)
      - Wrestling (Box E2)
    - Back to School (Box E2)
    - Band, 2 folders (Box E2)
      (see also E17 Band Trip and E19 Band Picture Day)
    - Bentley Historical Library (Box E2)
      (see Michigan Historical Collections)
    - Blood Donors (Box E2)
    - Boat Races (Box E2)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box E2)
    - Broadcasting (Box E3)
    - Buildings
      (see also E19 Campus Buildings)
      - Alumni Center (Box E3)
      - Angel Hall (Box E3)
      - Art and Architecture (Box E3)
      - Betsey Barbour (Box E3)
      - Burton Tower (Box E3)
      - Campus Safety Services (Box E3)
      - Canham Natatorium (Box E3)
      - East Hall (Box E3)
      - Economics (includes 1981 fire) (Box E3)
      - Go Blue Shop (Box E3)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Building (Box E3)
      - Fleming Administration (Box E3)
      - Gerald R. Ford Library (Box E3)
      - Hill Auditorium (Box E3)
      - Inglis House (Box E3)
      - Institute for Social Research (Box E3)
      - Institute of Continuing Legal Education (Box E3)
      - Law Library (Box E3)
      - Law Quad (Box E3)
      - Lurie Engineering Tower (Box E3)
      - Martha Cook (Box E3)
      - Media Union (Box E3)
      - Michigan League (Box E3)
      - Michigan Stadium (Box E3)
      - Michigan Union (Box E3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box E3)
      - Modern Languages (Box E4)
      - North Campus (Box E4)
      - Power Center (Box E4)
      - President's House (Box E4)
      - Rackham Building (Box E4)
      - Schembechler Hall (Box E4)
      - Waterman Gym (Box E4)
    - Business Administration (Box E4)
    - Campus Information Center (Box E4)
    - Campus Scenes, 3 folders (Box E4)
      (see also Student Activities and E19 Campus Scenes)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box E4)
    - Center for the Education of Women (Box E4)
    - Center for Japanese Studies (Box E4)
    - Chemistry (Box E4)
    - Children (Box E4)
    - Commencement (Folder 1 of 3) (Box E4)
      (includes Marian Anderson, 1959, Walter Cronkite, 1984, Lyndon B. Johnson, 1964)
      (see also E19 Commencements and Convocations)
    - Commencement (Folder 2 of 3) (Box E5)
    - Commencement (Folder 3 of 3) (Box E5)
    - Computers and Communication (Box E5)
    - Credit Union (Box E5)
    - CRISP Registration (Box E5)
      (see also Registration)
    - Dance (Box E5)
      (see also Music, School of)
    - Dearborn (Box E5)
    - Demonstrations 1960s (Box E5)
    - Dental School (Box E5)
    - Diag (Box E5)
    - Education, School of (Box E5)
    - Enact Teach-In March, 1970 (Box E5)
    - Energy Conservation (Box E5)
    - Engineering (Folder 1 of 3) (Box E5)
      (see also E19 Engineering)
    - Engineering (Folder 2 of 3) (Box E6)
    - Engineering (Folder 3 of 3) (Box E6)
    - Engineering, Nuclear (Box E6)
    - English Language Institute (Box E6)
    - Exhibit Museum of Natural History (Box E6)
    - Exhibits, Gifts, Awards (Box E6)
    - Extension Services (Box E6)
    - Faculty Award Winners (Box E6)
    - Family Recreation (Box E6)
    - Film (Box E6)
    - Firemanship Training (Box E6)
    - Flint College (Box E6)
    - Food Service (Box E6)
    - Forestry (Box E6)
    - Fraternities (Box E6)
    - Furstenberg Student Center (Medical School) (Box E6)
    - Geology (Box E6)
    - Gerontology (Box E6)
    - Health Services (Box E6)
    - Homecoming (Box E6)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box E6)
    - Housing (Box E6)
      (see also Residence Halls)
    - Institute for Science and Technology (Box E7)
    - Institute for Social Research (Box E7)
    - Interlochen (Box E7)
    - International Center (Box E7)
    - Japan Auto Conference 1981 (Box E7)
    - Journalism (Box E7)
    - Kelsey Museum (Box E7)
    - Labor (Box E7)
    - Laboratory Scenes (Box E7)
      (see also Research)
    - Law, 3 folders (Box E7)
      (see also Buildings-Law)
    - Law School Faculty
      - Portrait Photos, Pre-1981, 3 folders (Box E7)
      - Portrait Photos 1981-1984 (Box E8)
    - Legislature (Box E8)
    - Libraries (Box E8)
      (see also Michigan Historical Collections, William L. Clements Library, Taubman Medical Library, Rare Books)
    - Literature, Science, and the Arts (Box E8)
    - Mail Service (Box E8)
    - Medical Center
      (see also E19 University Hospital)
      - Buildings
        - Construction-Mott, Medical Science Research Building, Parking Structure (Box E8)
        - Kresge Medical Research Building Dedication (Box E8)
        - Medical School (Box E8)
        - Miscellaneous (Box E9)
        - Old Main Hospital (Box E9)
        - Clinical and Patient Care (Box E9)
        - Replacement Hospital Project
          - Construction (Box E9)
          - Moving Day (Box E9)
          - Planning and Groundbreaking (Box E9)
        - Ronald McDonald House Groundbreaking (Box E9)
        - W.K. Kellogg Eye Center Groundbreaking and Construction (Box E9)
      - Miscellaneous (Box E9)
      - Nurses and Nursing Services (Box E9)
      - Research (includes Dr. Christian Barnard) (Box E9)
      - Surgical Procedures (Box E9)
    - Men's Glee Club (Box E9)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box E9)
    - Meteorology (Box E9)
    - Michigan Awareness Program (Box E9)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box E9)
    - Michigan League (Box E9)
      (see also Buildings-Michigan League)
    - Michigan Union (Box E9)
      (see also Buildings-Michigan Union)
    - Minorities (Box E9)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box E10)
    - Miscellaneous-Contact Sheets (Box E10)
    - Museum of Art (Box E10)
    - Museums, 2 folders (Box E10)
      (see also Exhibit Museum of Natural History)
    - Music, School of, 3 folders (Box E10)
      (see also Dance and University Musical Society)
    - Musical Performances (Box E11)
    - Natural Resources (Box E11)
    - Nature Scenes (Box E11)
    - Naval Architecture / Marine Engineering (Box E11)
    - Near Eastern Studies (Box E11)
    - Non-University of Michigan Campus (Box E11)
    - North Campus Commons (Box E11)
    - Nursing, School of (Box E11)
    - Observatory (Box E11)
    - Ophthalmology (Box E11)
    - Parking (Box E11)
    - Peace Corps (includes image of Kennedy on Union steps na 7576) (Box E11)
      (See also E24 Kennedy Visit)
    - People
      (see also Presidents, Vice Presidents, Regents of the University)
      - Ford, Gerald; Mrs. Ford (Box E11)
        (includes 1974 visit)
      - Groups (Box E11)
      - Historical Reproductions (Box E11)
      - Life Magazine, Images Produced by (Box E11)
      - Non-Academic Staff (Box E11)
      - Non-University (Box E11)
      - Professional / Administrative Staff (Folder 1 of 2) (Box E11)
      - Professional / Administrative Staff (Folder 2 of 2 (Box E12)
      - Unidentified People (Box E12)
      - Visiting Dignitaries and Honorary Degrees (1) Leonard Bernstein, Jimmy Carter, Robert Frost, Lee Iacocca, Chiang Kai-Shek (Box E12)
      - Visiting Dignitaries and Honorary Degrees (2) Ferdinand Marcos, Imelda Marcos, Mao Tse Tung, Richard Nixon (Box E12)
      - Visiting Dignitaries and Honorary Degrees (3) McDivitt and White Convocation (Box E12)
      - Visiting Dignitaries and Honorary Degrees / Miscellaneous (4) (Box E12)
      - Visitors-General (Box E12)
    - Personnel / Benefits (Box E12)
    - Pharmacy (Box E12)
    - Phoenix Laboratory (Box E13)
    - Physical Therapy (Box E13)
    - Physics (Box E13)
      (see also E19 Physics)
    - Plant Department
      - Building Services (Box E13)
      - General (Box E13)
      - Landscaping and Grounds (Box E13)
      - Maintenance and Construction (Box E13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box E13)
      - Safety (Box E13)
    - Polio Images (Box E13)
    - Political, Miscellaneous (Box E13)
    - Power Center (Box E13)
      see also Buildings / Power Center
    - Presidents
      - Hatcher, Harlan (Box E13)
      - Fleming, Robert (Box E13)
      - Smith, Alan (Interim President) (Box E13)
    - President's Office (Box E13)
    - Project Community (Box E13)
    - Psychology (Box E14)
    - Public Health, School of (Box E14)
    - Rackham (Box E14)
    - Rare Books (Box E14)
    - Regents of the University (Box E14)
    - Regent's Cube (Box E14)
    - Registration (Box E14)
      (see also CRISP / Registration)
    - Religious Affairs, Office of (Box E14)
    - Research (Folder 1 of 3) (Box E14)
      (see also Laboratory Scenes and E19 Research)
    - Research (Folder 2-3 of 3) (Box E15)
    - Research-Great Lakes (Box E15)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) (Box E15)
    - Residential College (Box E15)
    - Residence Halls (Box E15)
      (see also Housing)
    - Romance Languages (Box E15)
    - Sculptures on Campus (Box E15)
    - Senate Assembly (Box E15)
    - Social Work, School of (Box E15)
    - Shady Trails Camp (Box E15)
    - Speech (Box E15)
    - Sportscasters (Box E15)
    - Story Picture File (Box E15)
    - Solar Car
      - Solar Car, Miscellaneous 1993-1997 (Negatives and Slides) (Box E15)
      - Sunrace 1990 (Contact Sheet) (Box E15)
      - Sunrace 1993 (Box E15)
      - World Solar Challenge 1993 (Negatives and Contact Sheets) (Box E15)
    - Student Activities
      (see also Campus Scenes and E19 Campus Life)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Holiday Activities (Box E15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box E15)
    - Student Services (Box E15)
    - Sunrace 1990, 1993 (Box E15)
    - Taubman Medical Library (Box E15)
    - Telephone (Centrex) (Box E15)
    - Television (Box E15)
    - Theater / Entertainment, 2 folders (Box E15)
      (see also Trueblood Theater)
    - Ticket Sales (Box E15)
    - Tisch Hall (Box E15)
    - Training Seminars (Box E15)
    - Transportation (Box E15)
    - Trueblood Theater (Box E15)
      (see also Theater / Entertainment)
    - United Way (Box E15)
    - University Club (Box E15)
    - University Musical Society (Box E15)
    - University Publications (Box E15)
    - University Press (Box E15)
    - Vice Presidents (Box E15)
    - Visitor's Center (Box E15)
    - William L. Clements Library (Box E15)
    - Willow Run Airport (Box E15)
    - Wolverine Tower (Box E15)
    - Zoology (Box E15)
  - Slides
    - Athletics
      - Football
        - 1971 (Illinois, Indiana, Ohio, Virginia) (Box E15)
        - 1974 (Box E15)
    - Band Trip to Russia and Eastern Europe 1961 (Box E15)
    - Medical Science Building (Box E15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box E15)
    - Rosenthal Sculpture Installation (Box E15)
    - Shady Trails Camp 1971-1988 (Box E15)
    - Solar Car
      - Solar Vision 1995 (Box E15)
      - University of Michigan Sunrunner Model April 1990 (Box E15)
      - World Solar Challenge 1993 (2 Folders, Contact Sheets Included) (Box E15)
    - Women's Hospital (Box E15)
  - Boxed Slides
    - Aerial views of central campus, north campus, and football stadium 1969 (Box E15)
    - Athletics
      - Aerial Views of Michigan Stadium (Ohio State football game, 1969) (Box E15)
      - Football picture day (and sideline shots) 1971 (Box E15)
      - Football picture day 1972-1973 (Box E15)
  - Oversize Print Files
    - Athletics (Box E19)
    - Aviation (Hydro-aeroplane landing, Whitehall, Michigan, 1914) (Box E19)
    - Band Picture Day (Box E19)
    - Boat Races (Box E19)
    - Campus Buildings
      (see also E1 Buildings, E18 Boxed Slides, I1 Aerial Photographs, and I1 Campus Buildings)
      - Aerial Views (Box E19)
      - Miscellaneous (Box E19)
      - Photograph Album of UM buildings circa 1950 (Box E19)
    - Campus Life-Students (Box E19)
    - Campus Scenes
      - Indoor (Box E19)
    - Outdoor
      - Unidentified (Box E19)
    - Commencements and Convocations
      - Lyndon B. Johnson (Box E19)
      - McDivitt-White (Box E19)
      - Various (Box E19)
    - Computer Center (Box E19)
    - Engineering (various demonstrations) (Box E19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box E19)
    - Music (Box E19)
    - People
      - Life Magazine story about the University of Michigan (Box E19)
        (see also E11 People)
      - Losh, Hazel ("Doc") (Box E19)
      - University Faculty and Staff (Box E19)
    - Physics-Teaching in the Elementary School (Box E19)
    - Research-Scientific-Unidentified (Box E19)
    - University Hospital (Box E19)
  - Negatives
    - A-Aerial Images (Box E20)
      - Angel Hall (Box E20)
    - C-Chemistry Building 1969 (Box E20)
    - F-Football, Team Photo 1970
      - Ford, Gerald and Mrs. Johnson April 7, 1977 (Box E20)
    - G-Gies, Dr. (Box E20)
    - H-Hill Auditorium
      - Hospital Construction (Box E20)
    - L-Law Library Construction
      - Law School Construction (Box E20)
    - M-Medical Center
      - Miscellaneous (Box E20)
    - M-Miscellaneous Continued (Box E21)
    - N-North Campus (Box E21)
    - P-Professor Rowe, Electrical Engineering (Box E21)
    - S-Stadium (Box E21)
    - T-Transportation Institute, Professor Greenshield Traffic Flow Study 1956 (Box E21)
    - W-Women in Science-Equity Agenda (Box E21)
  - Negatives and Prints
    - Artwork (Box E21)
    - Corner Health Center 1998 (Contact Sheet Only) (Box E21)
    - Crump, Dr. John with Patient, 1998. (Contact Sheet Only) (Box E21)
    - Football Season 1979
      - Michigan vs. Northwestern (Box E21)
      - Michigan vs. Ohio State (Box E21)
      - Michigan vs. Minnesota (Box E21)
      - Michigan vs. Wisconsin (Box E21)
      - Michigan vs. Indiana (Box E21)
      - Michigan vs. Michigan State (Box E21)
      - Michigan vs. Kansas (Contact Sheets Included) (Box E21)
      - Michigan vs. Notre Dame (Box E21)
    - Football, Team Photo 1971 (Box E21)
    - Orthopedic Research (Box E21)
    - White Coat Ceremony 1977 (Contact Sheet Only) (Box E21)
    - Biological Station (Box E21)
  - Prints
    - Biological Station (Box E21)
    - Rabbit Laser Eye Procedure (Box E21)
    - Solar Vision (Box E21)
  - Negatives-School of Business Administration
    - A-1985 (Box E22)
    - B-1984 (Box E22)
    - C-1983 (Box E22)
    - D-1982 (Box E22)
    - F-1979
      - Faculty Informal Portraits 1979 (Box E22)
    - G-1981 (Box E22)
    - H-1982 1981 (Box E22)
    - M-1987 (Box E23)
      - Miscellaneous (Box E23)
    - N-1988 (Box E23)
    - O-1989 (Box E23)
    - P-1990 (Box E23)
    - Q-1991 (Box E23)
    - R-1993 (Box E23)
    - S-1992 (Box E23)
    - T-1995 (Box E23)
    - U-1994 (Box E23)
    - V-(Year is Unknown) (Box E23)
    - W-1988 (Box E23)
    - X, Y, Z-1983-1984 (Box E23)
  - Slides
    - Aerial Images, Central Campus 1969-1976 (Box E24)
    - Ameriflux Tower (Box E24)
    - Anderson, Dave. Zero Gravity Experiment (Box E24)
    - Artificial Intelligence. High-School Students Visit to AI Lab (Box E24)
    - Barrera, E. 1995 (Box E24)
    - Biological Station 1995 (Box E24)
    - Blue Sky Measurements (Box E24)
    - Burns and Putnam, Nickel Particles (Box E24)
    - Central Campus 1982 (Box E24)
    - Chamberlain (Box E24)
    - Clarke, John. Earth and Ultra Violet Light
      - Jupiter (Box E24)
    - Datsko, Jim, Walking on Experimental Test Track (Box E24)
    - Denver, R. Tadpole/Toad Images (Box E24)
    - Dickens, Gerry. Geology-Phoenix Reactor 1995 (Box E24)
    - Experimental Measurements Laboratory Open House 1995 (Box E24)
    - Ev-Vivo Bone Marrow Bioreactor, RBC/WBC Under Microscope 1991 (Box E24)
    - Feldman, Russell, and Chang in Lab 1997 (Box E24)
    - Fisher, Dan. Large Animal Carcass 1993
      - Stone Tools (Box E24)
    - Football 1970-1974 (Box E24)
    - Herbarium 1995 (Box E24)
    - Hurricane Damage to Dominican Republic Botanical Garden (Box E24)
    - Hurricane Tracking and Bio-Kinetic Presentation 1996 (Box E24)
    - Ji, Jin, Auditory Brain Probe (Box E24)
    - Johnson, Sensor on Penny 1998 (Box E24)
    - Kennedy, John F. Visit to University of Michigan 1960 (Box E24)
    - King, George, Lake Nyos (Box E24)
    - Kopelman Sensor 1992 (Box E24)
    - Krisch, High-Energy Spin Physics 1995 (Box E24)
    - Manufacturing Story Packet, Microsensor 1995 (Box E24)
    - Mechanical Engineering Television Network (METN) Remote Classroom/Studio 1995 (Box E24)
    - Miscellaneous (Box E24)
    - Mitani, John, Gorillas (Box E24)